<!--
<abcsoffashion_~>
	<topic="">
		<name>
			topic
		</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>
</abcsoffashion_~>	

--- 13 Items ---
Acid-Wash Denim
Afro Hair
Afro Picks
A-Line (or Skater) Skirts and Dresses
Anchors
Androgynous Dressing
Ankle Bow Footwear
Ao Dai
Argyle
Army Green
Asymmetrical
Athleisure
Aviator Sunglasses
-->
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<abcsoffashion_a>
	<topic="A1">
		<name>Acid-Wash Denim</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Rather than clean or classic denim, denim washed in acid provides a tough looking pair of denim.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			I do not like acid-wash denim much at all.  I have not seen an actual pair of acid-wash denim that I like, nor would I recommend any acid-wash denim to any wardrobe.  It just looks tacky to me and not all that stylish in any sense.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>
	
	<topic="A2">
		<name>Afro Hair</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Afro hairstyles have long been popular.  Afro types range from bushy afros to curly afros.  Both males and females have afro hairstyles.  Often times, females have curly afros that nicely frame their faces.  Afros can also be about as natural of hairstyles as there is.  Often times, afro hairstyles can be tough to manage.  So one has to take certain measures to properly take care of and maintain afro hairstyles.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			Afro hair has always been cool.  Among females, curly afro hairstyles can look wonderful.  Don't diss the 'fro, bro/sis!  :)
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>
	
	<topic="A3">
		<name>Afro Picks</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			When you just want to show off your awesome afro with an equally awesome comb, try afro picks!  An afro pick is a quick go-to for when you want to comb your afro.  You can also just leave an afro pick in your afro to make a style statement!  Afro picks have tall brush pieces to properly comb through even the thickest of afros.  Afro picks themselves can be either plastic or metal.to take care of afros.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			Who doesn't love afros with afro picks?  Instant cool factor with these afro picks!  Solid!  :)
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>

	<topic="A4">
		<name>A-Line (or Skater) Dresses and Skirts</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			The A-Line (or skater) look is a classic styling exercise consisting of lower portions of dresses and skirts flaring out. For the girly-girl, this means one can have fun twirling such dresses and skirts.  An A-line dress can flare out from the bust line on to however long the dress is.  An A-line skirt can flare out from the waistline on down.  The skater namesake comes from the fact there are female ice skaters whose outfits have skirt portions that flare out.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			A-Line (or skater) garments are very airy and fun to me.  The way these garments flare out make them fun to wear and can be quite adorable.  I fancy a twirl-worthy dress or skirt.  An A-line, mini-length dress or skirt can be flirty.  Mid-length or longer make for lovely A-line dresses and skirts.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>

	<topic="A5">
		<name>Anchors</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Anchors are a quintessential element of nautical chic. There is a unique charm to nautical style as provided by anchors. They can be a bit on the tough side while not overdoing it.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			Anchors can be stylish whether having a garment dominated by a big anchor or having small anchors to accentuate an outfit.  It is best to have yourself a quality nautical-type outfit should you be wearing anything nautical.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>

	<topic="A6">
		<name>Androgynous Dressing</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			In most peoples’ minds, males should dress like males, and females should dress like females. NEVER should anyone try to dress as their opposite. You can easily break this rule in fashion if you like. In this respect, you should be able to dress up any way you please- even including males with feminine fashion elements or females with masculine fashion elements. There is a certain beauty towards dressing up and looking in ways of your opposite gender.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			Speaking as a male, I am not usually excited seeing females try to dress boyishly. That is not to say, however, that it is done wrong often times. I am a lot of times intrigued at males dressing feminine in regards to androgynous dressing. I have seen males dress up nicely feminine. Conversely, I have seen females who dress up nicely masculine. However you try to pull off such style is up to you. I just am more indifferent on whether I love or loathe these styling exercises.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>

	<topic="A7">
		<name>Ankle Bow Footwear</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Timeless pieces of feminine fashion are bows and ribbons. A designer named <a href="https://aminahabduljillil.com/">Aminah Abdul Jillil</a> popularized a pair of shoes that have a huge bow wraps cast aside.  The end result is a pair of shoes or sandals that wrap at the ankles with a big bow.  These shoes provide immense feminine and ladylike charm.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			You simply can not overstate the loveliness of a big bow on some sort of feminine garments.  Same applies for various shoes that have bow designs to them.  Some fashion bloggers really wear these beautiful ankle wrap shoes and sandals as beautifully as their wearers are.  My only recommendation is to try not to wear any garments that overpower the ankle-bow footwear.  Don't bombard yourself with multiple statement pieces.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>

	<topic="A8">
		<name>Ao Dai (Áo dài)</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			In Vietnamese culture, Ao Dai (pronounced: “oh-yai”) is a city in Vietnam as well as a beautiful folk outfit worn by Vietnamese females. The latter is (obviously) what I will discuss here. The Ao Dai is a formal-type outfit consisting of a long tunic dress worn over some white pants. Ao Dai suits usually feature a number of different color and pattern styles. These outfits are worn by Vietnamese adults as well as Vietnamese children.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			I think the Ao Dai is a beautiful folk outfit for Vietnamese females. I love seeing these outfits being worn and the style they provide.  The tunic dresses can either be plain or have any number of intricate designs and patterns to them.  Regardless, they are very beautiful to me as a folk outfit for Vietnamese females.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>

	<topic="A9">
		<name>Argyle</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Argyle patterns can be preppy, stylish, and to some… nerdy. No matter how you feel about argyle, its appeal is certainly there.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			I think argyle can be very cool.  Surely give it a try if you're the preppy type!
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="A10">
		<name>Army Green</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Even if you do not serve in the military, you can still incorporate military style in your wardrobe. Army Green is a popular color for which to sport outfits with. Army Green is a green color that almost has some brown in it. Since one wears Army-inspired garments, it is not required you get combat boots or anything to compliment the outfit. Though if you want to infuse military chic, then go with any number of military-style garments or perhaps even try out camouflage.  Army Green can be a great color for outfits.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			Army Green is a powerful color.  One has a lot of choices for which to go with Army Green outfits.  You certainly will be in your element if you can find a good set of Army Green garments to rock.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>

	<topic="A11">
		<name>Asymmetrical</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Most clothes are symmetrical in their design. Usually, though, some test various non-symmetrical styles. One of the most common are one-shoulder tops, dresses, and one-piece swimsuits.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			Some asymmetrical outfits can be quite chic.  For starters, a nice one-shoulder top can make for a very nice style statement.  The one thing I often wonder for fashionistas is if there is a certain preference they may have for what direction the asymmetrical piece is.  For example, would one prefer having an asymmetrical top with the non-symmetrical side on one's left or one's right.  Or would one prefer an asymmetrical skirt or dress to have a low hem on one's left/right and the higher hem on the right/left.  Either way, these garments can be very good to make a style statement with.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	

	<topic="A12">
		<name>Athleisure</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			One of the most popular styles of the past few years is that of athleisure. Think of “athleisure” as “athletic leisure.” This is a style that incorporates sporty elements while not being a proper athletic or active outfit. In other words, think of wearing a simple T-shirt and jean skirt outfit with a pair of active sneakers. Another example would be a proper office suit paired with some active sneakers. On the other hand, one female could have a rather chic look but by pairing active tops and/or bottoms with chic accessories or shoes. Imagine wearing fleece active pants and pair them with some stylish pumps or a chic pair of sandals or boots.  Likewise, certain fashionable types could go with a fairly chic and fashion outfit complimented by some kind of sporty sneakers or sporty slide sandals.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			This style can hit-or-miss to me. One thing I will tell you is the wrong pair of shoes can ruin any outfit. There is no problem going with some sort of sporty appeal to an outfit.  Just be wary not to ruin an overall balance by going with a poor footwear choice.  That even includes stupidly trying to pair sporty shoes that will ruin the balance or appeal of any sort of outfit.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>

	<topic="A13">
		<name>Aviator Sunglasses</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			One of the most popular styles of sunglasses are aviator sunglasses. The amount of coverage offered to these glasses is immense with their big lenses. They are often enjoyed by the likes of males and females alike.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			I am not as crazy about aviator sunglasses as most fashionable types are.  However, I'm sure for the coverage and the protection, you can probably do no wrong going with aviator sunglasses.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
</abcsoffashion_a>