<!--
<abcsoffashion_~>
	<topic="">
		<name>topic</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>
</abcsoffashion_~>	

Babydoll (Lingerie)
Babydoll (Style)
Backpacks
{Ballet Flats}
Band T-Shirts (or Band Tees)
Bandanas
Bandage (or BodyCon)
Bandeau
Bangles and Bracelets
~10~Bardot (or Off-Shoulder)
Barefoot Sandals
Baseball Caps
Baseball T-Shirts (or Raglan Baseball Tees)
Basketball Sneakers
Basketball Shorts
Beach Curls
Beanie Caps
Bell Bottoms
Bell Sleeve
~20~Beige
{Berets}
{Bike Shorts}
Bikinis
Bikini Briefs
Birthstones
Black Jeans
Bleached Denim
Blindfolds
Blouses
~30~Blouses With Bows
Blush Pink
Board Shorts
Boat Shoes
Boatneck
Bob Hairstyles
BodyCon Dresses and BodyCon Skirts
Body Chains
Bodysuits
Boiler Suits (or Boilersuits)
~40~Bomber Jackets
Bowties
Boxers
Bras
{Bralets/Bralettes}
Briefs
{Brooches}
Bohemian Chic
Bootcut Jeans and Pants
Booties
~50~Boots Tucked Into Jeans/Pants/Leggings
“Borrowed From the Boys”
Bowling Shirts
Bowling Shoes
Boy Shorts
Boyfriend Fashion
Brogues
Bubblegum Pink
Burgundy (or Oxblood)
Bustiers
~60~Busted Knee Jeans and Pants
Butt Graphics
-->
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<abcsoffashion_B>
	<topic="B1">
		<name>Babydoll (Lingerie)</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			A babydoll in lingerie is often a camisole tunic.  These babydolls flare outward from the bust line.  Babydolls can be or can split down the middle up front.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>
	
	<topic="B2">
		<name>Babydoll (Style)</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Adorably feminine is how I would describe babydoll style. Tiered and loose fitting garments define babydoll garments. Some of the most girly styles are expressed with babydoll-style garments. If you feel the need to dumb down the girly appeal, tough shoes (like combat boots) are as much a girl’s best friend as diamonds in this regard.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			Babydoll fashion items can be totally adorable.  A simple babydoll top can be airy and fun to wear.  Babydoll dresses can be equally adorable.  I have no problem whatsoever with these babydoll fashion items.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>

	<topic="B3">
		<name>Backpacks</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Backpacks are a functional and cool way to carry around books and other supplies for school or college/university.  Fashion backpacks can be just as fun for carrying around other supplies and other personal items.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>

	<topic="B4">
		<name>Back Pocketless</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			A style advantage to having back pockets is that they can bring attention to you from behind.  Back pocketless bottoms, however, do not have any pockets on the back.  They are therefore a style deal allowing for a slim view of the rear.  Some in fashion are not as fond of back pocketless bottoms since they do not help add any style to one's backside.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			Not having back pockets does not mean such bottoms lack style.  Having such stylish back pockets help enhance one's rear view.  Bottoms with no back pockets can almost provide a legging-like appearance with a pair of jeans, pants, or shorts without any noticeable pockets.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>

	</topic>
<!--
		<name>Band T-Shirts (or Band Tees)</name>
		<image>...image...</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
-->
	<topic="B5">
		<name>Ballet Flats</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Ballet flats are named for the slippers worn by ballerinas.  Ballet flats mostly compliment simple outfits or provide a cute pair of shoes to wear for their simple slip-on comfort.  For having a different pair of shoes to switch to, there are even foldable flats that can go with you and ready to wear when you want something more comfortable to wear on your feet.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			Ballet flats are about the simplest chic shoes a female can ask for.  Slip-on, flat, and often times an adorable compliment to any outfit.  Their simplicity and style alone are enough to warrant getting them!
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			If you are interested in getting your own pair of ballet flats, take a look at the material I have provided for you here:

<insert_widget_here>

Happy shopping!  :)
		</resources>
	</topic>

	<topic="B6">
		<name>Bandage (or BodyCon)</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Bandage-type garments for females are body-hugging and appealing.  Also known as bodycon (for body-conscious), bandage garments usually come in the form of bandage skirts and bandage dresses.  Do not confuse the bandage deal in regards to being hurt and needing bandages to heal from a cut or some other deal.  These are slim-fitting (mostly) skirts and dresses that accentuate the body.  These garments can be appealing for various body types.  Even plus-size figures can enjoy the body-hugging appeal of bandage garments.  A number of fashionistas usually pair such bandage dresses and skirts with chic pairs of pumps, sandals, or boots.  Some even wear bandage dresses and skirts with sneakers.  Their versatility can even go into wearing these casually or for a night out.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			Bandage garments can be hot!  If you're feeling hot and want to accentuate your curves, give bandage dresses and skirts a try!
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>		
	</topic>

	<topic="B7">
		<name>Bandanas</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>

	<topic="B8">
		<name>Bandeau</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Bandeau represents tops that horizontally wrap around a female's breasts.  Bandeau tops and bras have no straps to them.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>

	<topic="B9">
		<name>Bangles and Bracelets</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>

	<topic="B10">
		<name>Bardot (or Off-Shoulder)</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>

	<topic="B11">
		<name>Barefoot Sandals</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Sandals provide open-air comfort.  Barefoot sandals are not proper sandals, but are instead like a headdress for your feet.  They are great for walking along the beach.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B12">
		<name>Baseball Caps</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B13">
		<name>Baseball T-Shirts (or Raglan Baseball Tees)</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	

	<topic="B14">
		<name>Basketball Shorts</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>		
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B15">
		<name>Basketball Sneakers</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B16">
		<name>Beach Curls</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Curly hair can be beautiful as it is.  Beach curls are stylish for the beachy and/or Bohemian set.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			I personally fancy curly hair the most.  If you are the beach or adventurous type, you can do no wrong than go with beach curls.  You do not even need to be the beach type to enjoy beach curls.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B17">
		<name>Beanie Caps</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			A casual and warm cap to wear during cool or cold days is a beanie cap.  Beanie caps can range from solid colors to patterned types.  They may even have tassels or other designs to help enhance the appeal of such caps.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			Definitely consider wearing beanie caps on cold days.  They provide ample protection and warmth for when it is cold.  You may want to wear a heavier jacket or coat with a beanie cap for more warmth for your head.  Preferably, a jacket or coat with a hood attached to it.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B18">
		<name>Beige</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>		
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B19">
		<name>Bell Bottoms</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Bell bottoms are jeans and pants with massively flared legs. They have been iconic as counterculture especially in the times of Woodstock in the 1960s with hippies. They enjoyed further style in the 1970s and were just as iconic then as they were during the late 1960s. Today, bell bottom jeans and pants are still stylish, and many would wear these massively-flared jeans and pants than wear skinny jeans and skinny pants. The silhouette of bell bottoms allow for the illusion of longer legs. Bohemian and vintage types often pair bell bottoms with bell sleeve tops or Bohemian style peasant tops. Some go with either flat footwear or some sort of platform footwear to compliment bell bottoms. While bell bottoms have been worn by males and females, bell bottoms in this day and age are mostly worn by females.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			Bell bottoms will NEVER go out of style regardless of what skinny jean and skinny pant types daresay. The funky, groovy appeal of bell bottoms are wonderful.  What may be a problem, however, are fashionable types of different heights wearing bell bottoms. For example, a petite female may seem swallowed up proportionally by wearing bell bottoms. Some petites even find a pair of cropped bell bottoms to better suit their petite frames.

Regardless of whether you fancy modest bells or massive bells,feel free to rock this style as best as you can.  It is not going away any time soon no matter what skinny bottoms types daresay.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B20">
		<name>Bell Sleeves</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B21">
		<name>Beret Caps</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B22">
		<name>Bike Shorts</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B23">
		<name>Bikini Briefs</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Bikini briefs are a style of underwear bottoms mostly worn by males.  They can be thought of as a somewhat romantic pair of bottoms that combine the comfort of briefs with the appealing coverage provided by bikini bottoms.  While most bikini briefs are for males, there are, of course, feminine bikini briefs.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			These bikini briefs can be pretty appealing for both males and females.  This underwear can provide some romantic appeal.  They can also be a fine alternative to those who don't want to wear something overpowering for underwear- like thongs.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B24">
		<name>Bikinis</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Named for a South Pacific island that suffered the impact of an atomic bomb, bikinis are a huge part of feminine fashion for beach/surf/resort chic.  Bikinis consist of a bathing suit top and bathing suit bottoms.  Most bikinis come in sets.  However, some bikini tops and bikini bottoms are mixed and matched.  So you do not have to have (for example) a white floral bikini top paired with matching white floral bikini bottoms.  Instead, you could wear a white floral bikini top paired with some solid pink bikini bottoms.  It is up to you- all you should know is that bikinis are fine to wear in beach/surf/resort situations.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			There are many kinds of bikinis ranging from bikini sets to separates.  Try to find a bikini set you will enjoy when ready to do some sunbathing or having fun in a beach/surf/resort setting.  Most important to wearing any sort of swimwear is to be confident in your own skin and body while wearing such charming swimwear (let alone bikinis).  In addition, do not feel you have to be incredibly slim to wear a bikini.  Not everyone has a "bikini body."
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>		

	<topic="B25">
		<name>Birthstones</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>			
	
	<topic="B26">
		<name>Black Denim</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			When it comes to denim, wearing black denim offers the comfort and style of basic blue denim along with the slimming effects of wearing black.  Black is also usually a popular color for edgy or Goth-style looks.  In some instances, some can get away with wearing black denim even for some semi-formal occasions or settings.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B27">
		<name>Bleached Denim</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Bleached denim features denim that has been badly damaged and usually in lighter than usual washes.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B28">
		<name>Blindfolds</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B29">
		<name>Blouses</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B30">
		<name>Blouses With Bows</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B31">
		<name>Blush Pink</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B32">
		<name>Board Shorts</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	

	<topic="B33">
		<name>Boatneck</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>	
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B34">
		<name>Boat Shoes (or Deck Shoes)</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			The concept of boat shoes originated in 1935.  What would be enjoyed today by males and females alike could be owed to what was originated by Sperry Top-Sider.  Boat shoes are often seen like sneakers.  Only difference is that boat shoes are not as casual as any average pair of sneakers.  However, they are not anything formal either.  So boat shoes are more of middle ground- not really sneakers, but not at all formal shoes.  Boat shoes even provide some preppy vibes.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			I honestly have never had a problem with boat shoes.  Their unisex style makes them fashionable for both males and females alike.  Any sort of casual or semi-casual outfit for males will go well with boat shoes as the footwear of choice.  For females, I always though boat shoes look cute either with cropped  jeans/pants or shorts of various lengths.  I never considered them really stylish with skirts and dresses.  If you do not want to wear sneakers but have a stylish pair of lace-up shoes, then boat shoes are a great option for you.  The most common color combination for boat shoes is usually linen and oat.  However, you are always free to try boat shoes in any combination of colors to compliment your outfits.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B33">
		<name>Bob Hairstyles</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>		
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B34">
		<name>BodyCon</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>	
	</topic>

	<topic="B35">
		<name>Body Chains</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
<!--

-
		<name>Bowties</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>		
	</topic>	
-->	
	<topic="B36">
		<name>Bodysuits</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			A bodysuit combines a top with a bikini-like bottom.  Think of bodysuits kind of like one-piece swimsuits- only you do not have to wear these to the beach or at some resort.  The advantage to bodysuits is that they can be worn without having to worry about keeping them tucked into bottoms.  So pair bodysuits with any number of bottoms and enjoy the style benefits!
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>	
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B37">
		<name>Bohemian Chic</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			From Bohemia to the popular "Bohemian Rhapsody," at some point, you have had at least some exposure to Bohemia.  Bohemia relates to a portion of the western section of what is now the Czech Republic.  Bohemian chic (also popularly called "Boho" chic) is wildly popular for especially warm weather times.  While I personally do not fully understand what makes outfits Bohemian, I mostly know Bohemian chic to be adventurous while also being immensely fun and casual.  Bohemian chic is especially popular among the festival crowd.  You will especially see Bohemian styles expressed at various outdoor festivals such as Coachella.

For the most part, Bohemian chic is seen in a number of different ways with a few different pieces.  Basic Bohemian chic can include things like cowboy hats, denim jean shorts, cowboy boots, various Western-style ankle boots, and more.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>	
	</topic>	

	<topic="B38">
		<name>Boiler Suits (or Boilersuits)</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Boilersuits are utilitarian jumpsuits worn by males and females.  The namesake comes from boilersuits worn mostly in coal-fired boiler rooms.  Though these are mostly worn by males, there are feminine versions just as blue collar as any regular boilersuits.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	

	<topic="B39">
		<name>Bomber Jackets</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>	
	</topic>

	<topic="B40">
		<name>Bootcut Jeans and Pants</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			I define bootcut jeans and pants as bottoms that have modest flares to them.  The flares of bootcut jeans and pants are minimal while still providing the right amount of flare to make them stylish.  As their namesake suggests, bootcut jeans and pants were meant to nicely be worn with boots.  That is, of course, granted they are not boots with wildly tall or expressive shafts to them.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B41">
		<name>Booties</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Booties can mean one of two things- either a pair of boots that go no higher than the ankles, or they may be a pair of socks that go no higher than the ankles.  I will mostly mention the former here.  Booties can be fashionable all year long.  For the most part, booties can be fashionable all year long since you do not have such tall shafts like usually taller pairs of boots.  So the ones who wear booties can enjoy boot appeal only without the tall shafts most boots have.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
<!--		
		<name>Bras</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
---
		<name>Boxers</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
---
		<name>Bralets/Bralettes</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>	
---
		<name>Briefs</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>		
-->		
	<topic="B42">
		<name>Boots Tucked Into Jeans/Pants/Leggings</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			If you do not want to soil the bottoms of your jeans or pants trudging through mud, snow piles, or high water; you can wear a tall pair of boots over your jeans or pants.  These provide comfort and even warmth while walking through such surfaces or areas.  This is a fashion style very popular among females.  A lot of females (and some males) enjoy wearing tall boots to wear over their jeans or pants.  Usually, this is most common with jeans more than certain pants.  What become an issue is how to properly wear boots over jeans or pants.  Some try to wear tall socks to make tucking jeans or pants into boots a bit easier.  Regardless, this is a classic fashion exercise that has mostly been popular again starting in the mid-2000s.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			I actually hated this look for when it is not cold or tough to walk in.  Over time, though, I began to like this look.  I think cold weather times often present the opportunity for fashionistas to wear their most fabulous pairs of boots.  I began to appreciate the look from a style standpoint eventually.  Even a basic pair of boots tucked into jeans or pants can still be plenty stylish for those who work the trend properly.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>	
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B43">
		<name>Brooches</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B44">
		<name>Bootcut Jeans and Pants</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B45">
		<name>Booties</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B46">
		<name>"Borrowed From the Boys"</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B47">
		<name>name</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B48">
		<name>Bowling Shirts</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B49">
		<name>Bowling Shoes</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B50">
		<name>Boy Shorts</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Boy shorts are lingerie bottoms offering the coverage a pair of short shorts provide.  Boy shorts are stylish as lingerie and even as swimwear bottoms.  The namesake of boy shorts doesn't mean these are shorts worn by boys.  It is not recommended that boy shorts to be worn as any casual wear.  You are better served wearing short shorts, hot pants, or whatever.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B51">
		<name>Boyfriend Fashion</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Boyfriend fashion is predicated on masculine-style garments cut for a feminine figures.  The style became popularized in the sense that boyfriend chic stems from females wearing clothing from their boyfriends.  In fact, boyfriend fashion was popularized by Katie Holmes, who wore Tom Cruise's clothes out and about after a Broadway rehearsal.  This style is commonly seen as romantic in the sense of any female wearing the clothing from her boyfriend.  The most common boyfriend fashion items are usually boyfriend jeans or even boyfriend shorts.  Also popular are boyfriend blazers.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			My male crowd may have mixed reactions in regards to females wearing male clothes, but the mood mostly seems romantic when a female you're with takes off your clothes and wear them as their own outfits.  Personally, I am not much fond of boyfriend fashion, especially that of boyfriend jeans.  The silhouette and style of boyfriend jeans just seems off and not stylish in the least sense to me.  At least, I've expressed dislike of boyfriend denim.  You females, of course, can debate as much as you like with boyfriend fashion.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B52">
		<name>Brogues</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B53">
		<name>Bubblegum Pink</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			Bubblegum Pink is a punchy pink color.  As the name suggests, its color resembles your average pink bubble gum.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			For its color, this is a great color to offset any standard sort of dark or dull colors.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B54">
		<name>Burgundy (or Oxblood)</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B55">
		<name>Bustiers</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B56">
		<name>Busted Knee Jeans and Pants</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B57">
		<name>Butt Graphics</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			If you want to call attention to your backside, look for bottoms that have graphics on the butt.  Such graphics could include certain words or images plastered on the butt.
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			These bottoms can provide attention to your backside.  Sometimes, though… unnecessary attention.  In no way do I hate this styling exercise.  I am just more along the lines of... be careful sporting such bottoms.  It is just something to be cautious of rather than a style to completely avoid.
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
<!--	
	<topic="B58">
		<name>Back Pocketless</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B59">
		<name>topic</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B60">
		<name>topic</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>	
	
	<topic="B61">
		<name>topic</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>
	
	<topic="B62">
		<name>topic</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>
	
	<topic="B63">
		<name>topic</name>
		<image>
			<IMG SRC="" ALT="">
			(Source: )
		</image>
		<discussion>
			intro
		</discussion>
		<thoughts>
			opinion
		</thoughts>
		<resources>
			...resources...
		</resources>
	</topic>
-->	
</abcsoffashion_B>